The "My Child" website is a password protected portal for parents
‘My Child’웹사이트는 비밀번호로 보호된 포털로
to view their child's progress while at Bodwell.
부모님이 보드웰에서 학생의 경과를 볼 수 있습니다
To begin, we recommend Chrome or Safari as the site is optimized for these platforms.
최적화된 실행을 위해 크롬이나 사파리를 추천해드립니다
There are a number of ways to reach the portal. You can go through our website at bodwell.edu
포털에 접속하기 위한 방법은 다양한데 bodwell.edu 에서
and then find the ".community" tab
‘Community’탭을 눌러서 찾거나
or by typing mychild.bodwell.edu directly into you browser.
브라우저에서 mychild.bodwell.edu를 직접 치면 됩니다
To log in, you must have a verified e-mail with the school.
로그인하기 위해서는 학교로부터 인증 메일을 받아야 합니다
Your log in credentials will be sent to your email and updated each term
로그인 정보는 이메일로 보내지고 매 학기 업데이트 됩니다
Once logged in, you are taken to the "My Child" dashboard
로그인이 되면‘My Child’대시보드가 보이는데
which is an overview of all of child's information.
여기에는 학생의 모든 전반적인 정보가 나와있습니다
There are 7 components to this dashboard.
대시보드는 7가지로 구성되어 있습니다
The 4 tabs at the top; we are currently on the first tab labelled "My Child".
현재 상단의 4개의 탭 중 첫번째인‘My Child’탭 입니다
Second is your child's information including the house and hall they belong to,
두번째는 학생이 속한 하우스와 홀 그리고
and how long they have been enrolled at Bodwell.
보드웰 재학 기간을 포함한 정보가 있습니다
This section is for general announcements and reminders.
이 섹션은 일반적인 소식 및 상기 내용입니다
This is the academic overview of your child
이 것은 학생의 전반적 학업 현황인데
You have a quick glance at the current courses, grades well as their attendance.
현재 듣고 있는 수업의 성적 및 출석을 훑어볼 수 있습니다
A more detailed look at each student's academics can be found under the "Academic Record" tab
학업에 관한 더 자세한 내용은 잠시 뒤에 나올
explained in a moment
‘Academic Record’탭에서 확인할 수 있습니다
The next component is a summary of your child's participation hours
다음은 학생의 참여 시간 요약입니다
Again, a more detailed breakdown can be found under the third  tab labelled"Student Life Record".
더 자세한 내용은 세번째 탭인‘Student Life Record’에서 볼 수 있습니다
Below that is a term timeline identifying important dates.
그 아래는 중요 날짜가 표기된 타임라인입니다
You can move forward or backward by using the arrows.
화살표를 사용해서 앞이나 뒤로 이동할 수 있습니다
Lastly, a list of staff involved in your child's life at Bodwell.
마지막은 보드웰에서 학생과 관련된 모든 스텝들입니다
The first column is teachers of their academic subjects
첫번재 열은 학과 과목의 선생님입니다
The second is their extra-cirriccular teachers including E-Block, clubs, and teams.
두번째는 토요 심화학습, 클럽, 팀 등의 교과외활동 선생님입니다
Third, their counsellors and their advisors.
세번째는 카운셀러와 상담가입니다
Lastly, the principals.
마지막으로 교장 선생님입니다
Back to the tabs, clicking "Academic Record"
탭으로 돌아가서 ‘Academic Record’를 누르면
will bring you to a more detailed look at your child's courses.
학생이 듣는 수업에 관하여 더 자세한 내용을 볼 수 있습니다
We call this the "Grade Book"
보드웰에서는 이를 ‘Grade Book’이라고 부릅니다
Clicking this box, a list of current courses will drop down.
이 박스를 누르면 현재 듣고 있는 수업 목록이 보입니다
The second box on the right will reveal components that will make up the grade
오른편의 두번째 박스는 성적을 구성하는 요소들을 나타내고
and how it is weighted for the final mark.
최종 성적이 어떻게 매겨지는지
In this example, we can see that assignments are worth 20% of the final grade,
예를 들어 최종 성적의 20%가 숙제
quizzes 5% and tests 40%.
퀴즈 5%, 테스트 40% 로 구성되어 있는 것을 볼 수 있습니다
Below we can see the results of each of those components as they happen.
그 아래 각 구성 요소의 자세한 내용과 결과를 볼 수 있습니다
Results are recorded and posted by teachers as soon as they are completed.
선생님은 결과가 나오는대로 기록하며 기재합니다
The "Student Life Record" is a detailed look at their participation hours.
‘Student Life Record’는 학생의 참여 시간을 보여줍니다
The first box reveals which term we are looking at
첫번째 박스는 학기를 나타냅니다
and the second is the type of participation recorded.
두번째는 참여한 활동의 종류를 나타냅니다
There are 4 types of participation hours
참여 시간은 졸업을 위한 봉사 활동 및 직업 체험 시간 외에도
as well as their volunteer and work experience hours which are required for graduation.
4가지의 종류가 있습니다
Below, all the details for each entry including
그 아래 각 항목의 자세한 내용과
which staff member has logged the hours.
어떤 스텝이 참여 시간을 기록했는지 나옵니다
The last tab is the "Bodwell Explained" tab
마지막 탭은‘보드웰 설명’탭으로
which is a video library of common questions and issues.
자주하는 질문과 주제에 관한 영상 그리고
as well as an inside look at a students life here at Bodwell.
보드웰에서 학생들의 생활을 보여주는 영상이 있습니다
Videos are divided into two main categories,
영상은 ‘학업’ 그리고 ‘생활’
"Academic" and "Student Life" videos.
두개의 메인 카테고리로 나뉘어져 있습니다
To begin, simply click on the video or the topic that you are interested in,
시작하려면 간단히 영상이나 관심있는 주제를 클릭해서
and a video window should pop up.
영상이 나오는 창을 띄우게 됩니다
Begin by pressing play.
플레이를 눌러서 시작하세요
The bottom right corner has subtitle language.
우측 하단 코너에서는 자막을 선택할 수 있는데
Here, we will make as many languages as possible available.
최대한 다양한 언어가 준비되어 있습니다
By clicking on the top right corner you can enter the fullscreen mode.
우측 상단 코너를 클릭하면 전체 화면 모드를 열 수 있습니다
Please exit this mode by pressing "esc".
종료를 원하시면‘Esc’를 누르면 됩니다
Finally, to return to the main dashboard page,
마지막으로 메인 대시보드 페이지로 돌아가려면
simply click on the "My Child" tab here.
간단히 ‘My Child’탭을 클릭하면 됩니다
Clicking on "Home" will refresh the page and may take a moment,
‘Home’을 누르면 페이지가 새로고침되어 잠시 기다려야 합니다
however, it will also refresh the information.
이로써 정보 또한 새로고침 될 것입니다
If you have any questions or have trouble logging in,
만약 로그인하는데 문제가 있다면
please contact Helpdesk.mychild@bodwell.edu for more information.
Mychild.helpdesk@bodwell.edu 로 문의주시기 바랍니다
Here's how you can add the My Child website to the home screen of your mobile device.
다음은 스마트폰에 My Child 웹사이트를 등록하는 방법입니다
Simply open "My Child" in your browser
브라우저에서‘My Child’를 여세요
Click on "options" and click "add to home screen".
‘옵션’을 누르고‘홈스크린에 추가’를 누르세요
confirm by pressing "add",
‘추가’를 눌러서 컨펌하세요
And the "My Child" parent portal will appear as an icon on your home screen for easy access.
이제‘My Child’포털을 홈스크린에서 쉽게 접속할 수 있습니다